https://www.robolights.co.uk/help/privacy-policy

Privacy PolicyWe collect certain information from you; when you register, place an order, or enter information on our site.When ordering or registering, you will be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience and allow us to fulfill or services to you as a customer.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our updates, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features to quickly process your transactions, and to send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.HOW DO WE PROTECT VISITOR INFORMATION?We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information. All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.DO WE USE 'COOKIES'?We use the following cookies on our site:Cookies set by the framework this site is running upon, this allows the website to distinguish you, as a visitor, as you're using our website and/or making a purchase from our online commerce systemCookies set by Google Analytics, helping us to measure how users interact with our website and content.THIRD PARTY DISCLOSUREWe do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.THIRD PARTY LINKSWe do not include or offer third party products or services on our website.
